<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lako</string>
    <string name="web_id">AIzaSyAk17eFI8jtknqc84CLLLqpmuyZDzeWB8c</string>
    <string name="banner_image">Mabuhay Shop with Lako Banner</string>

    <string name="under"><u>Add List Product</u></string>
    <string name="password"><u>Forgot Password?</u></string>
    <string name="resend_code"><u>Resend OTP</u></string>


    <string name="signIn"><b><u>Sign In.</u></b></string>
    <string name="signUp"><b><u>Sign Up.</u></b></string>


    <string name="about_us">Welcome to Lakò, your mobile platform for supporting local
        creative sellers! At Lakò, we are dedicated to bridging the gap between talented
        local artists and a broader audience by providing a centralized, curated e-commerce
        space exclusively for showcasing handcrafted products. Our mission is to empower local
        artisans, offering them the tools and resources needed to optimize sales, enhance customer
        engagement, and gain the recognition they deserve.\n \nLakò was born out of the need to address the
        challenges faced by local artists in connecting with potential customers. Traditional e-commerce platforms
        often overshadow these artisans with established brands, limiting their visibility and sales opportunities.
        Our platform is designed to eliminate this competition, creating a community-driven marketplace where local
        talent can thrive. \n \nWith features like visually appealing profile showcases, direct messaging for inquiries,
        a personalized explore feed, organized product categories, community chat, and promotional tools, Lakò ensures a
        seamless and supportive experience for both sellers and buyers.</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions"><b>Terms and Conditions</b> \n \n<b>Last Revised:</b> June 4, 2024 \n \n Welcome to Lako. This mobile e-commerce application is provided as a service to our users and may be used for informational and purchasing purposes only.
        Because the Terms and Conditions contain legal obligations, please read them carefully. \n\n<b>1. Eligibility Criteria:</b> \n \nUsers must be at least 18 years old to create an account, provide accurate and complete information, and comply with all local
        laws and regulations regarding online purchases. \n \n<b>2. Account Registration:</b> \n\nBy creating an account, you agree to provide truthful information and maintain the
        confidentiality of your login credentials. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your account. \n \n<b>3. Product Listings and Availability:</b> \n \nProduct descriptions and availability are
        subject to change without notice. We strive to ensure accuracy but do not guarantee that product listings, images, or other content will be error-free. \n \n <b>4. Pricing and Payment:</b> \n \nAll prices are listed in PHP and are subject to change.
        Payment must be made at the time of purchase through the accepted payment methods. Any applicable taxes and shipping charges will be added at checkout. \n \n <b>5. Shipping and Delivery:</b> \n \nWe offer various shipping options, which will be outlined during
        the checkout process. Delivery times are estimates and not guaranteed. We are not responsible for delays caused by shipping carriers or unforeseen circumstances. \n \n <b>6. Returns and Refunds:</b> \n \nOur return policy allows for returns within
        30 days of purchase for most items. Items must be returned in their original condition. Refunds will be processed in accordance with our return policy, which is available on our website. \n \n <b>7. Use of Information:</b> \n \nBy using our app, you consent to the collection,
        use, and disclosure of your personal and transactional information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We prioritize privacy and security in compliance with applicable laws and regulations. \n \n <b>8. User Conduct:</b> \n \nUsers agree not to engage
        in any activities that may harm Lako, its users, or third parties. This includes but is not limited to fraud, harassment, spamming, or any other illegal or harmful behavior. \n \n <b>9. Modification and Termination:</b> \n \nWe reserve the right to modify
        or terminate these terms and conditions at any time without prior notice. Changes will be communicated to users promptly. Continued use of the app constitutes acceptance of the revised terms. \n \n <b>10. Governing Law:</b> \n \nThese terms and conditions are
        governed by the laws of the Philippines. Any disputes arising out of or in connection with these terms and conditions shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in the Philippines. \n \nBy using the Lako app, you acknowledge that
        you have read, understood, and agree to abide by these terms and conditions. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us for clarification before proceeding with your use of the app.
    </string>

    <string name="terms">By signing up, you agree to our <b><u>Terms and Conditions.</u></b></string>
</resources>